[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Have a seat right here.", "answer_tokens": ["Have", "a", "seat", "right", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Why can't we live like this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "we", "live", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "You know, I was -- I had to use the bathroom before I came out here.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "was", "--", "I", "had", "to", "use", "the", "bathroom", "before", "I", "came", "out", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 96, "question": "When you were a young little guy in -- in Indianapolis, did anybody inspire you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "a", "young", "little", "guy", "in", "--", "in", "Indianapolis", ",", "did", "anybody", "inspire", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Indianapolis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bing Crosby"]}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Did you have a favorite comedian or a comic or somebody?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "a", "favorite", "comedian", "or", "a", "comic", "or", "somebody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "I mean it wasn't Bing Crosby.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "was", "n't", "Bing", "Crosby", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "And I just thought there's something very cool about this.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "just", "thought", "there", "'s", "something", "very", "cool", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "This is Merv right there?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "Merv", "right", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "This is Merv.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "Merv", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "1969?", "question_tokens": ["1969", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Did you -- did you have an eye for the show business at that point?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "--", "did", "you", "have", "an", "eye", "for", "the", "show", "business", "at", "that", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, it's a silly story, but where better to tell a silly story than here with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "silly", "story", ",", "but", "where", "better", "to", "tell", "a", "silly", "story", "than", "here", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "But that's -- and I -- I can remember doing so poorly my mom was very upset about it and she said we're going to try to get you into a trade school.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "that", "'s", "--", "and", "I", "--", "I", "can", "remember", "doing", "so", "poorly", "my", "mom", "was", "very", "upset", "about", "it", "and", "she", "said", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "try", "to", "get", "you", "into", "a", "trade", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Isn't that nice?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "nice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "So then I -- then I stopped worrying so much about other things and just knew that all I have to do is find a way that you can get paid for what I thought I can do.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "then", "I", "--", "then", "I", "stopped", "worrying", "so", "much", "about", "other", "things", "and", "just", "knew", "that", "all", "I", "have", "to", "do", "is", "find", "a", "way", "that", "you", "can", "get", "paid", "for", "what", "I", "thought", "I", "can", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "And when did the comedy phase hit you that you wanted to be a comedian, you wanted to get involved in comedy?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "did", "the", "comedy", "phase", "hit", "you", "that", "you", "wanted", "to", "be", "a", "comedian", ",", "you", "wanted", "to", "get", "involved", "in", "comedy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Well, as a kid, I think most kids are always funny.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "a", "kid", ",", "I", "think", "most", "kids", "are", "always", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "So one night you just packed up and drove to Hollywood?", "question_tokens": ["So", "one", "night", "you", "just", "packed", "up", "and", "drove", "to", "Hollywood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Well, in a matter of speaking, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "a", "matter", "of", "speaking", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "No, I'm coming across the table if you roll another tape.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "coming", "across", "the", "table", "if", "you", "roll", "another", "tape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "It really bothers you that much?", "question_tokens": ["It", "really", "bothers", "you", "that", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I don't want anymore tape.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "anymore", "tape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "You think so?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Fine, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Fine", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Miss Letterman, can I ask you a question?", "question_tokens": ["Miss", "Letterman", ",", "can", "I", "ask", "you", "a", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Letterman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Has he ever told you that?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "ever", "told", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Yes, he talks about it frequently.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "talks", "about", "it", "frequently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Did you have a good relationship with Johnny?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "a", "good", "relationship", "with", "Johnny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Yes, but he made me very nervous because he was, I think, the biggest star on television.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "he", "made", "me", "very", "nervous", "because", "he", "was", ",", "I", "think", ",", "the", "biggest", "star", "on", "television", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "Jack Paar?", "question_tokens": ["Jack", "Paar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Paar"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Do you understand what I'm saying?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I understand exactly what you're saying.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "understand", "exactly", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "But did you have a chance to tell him what he meant to you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "have", "a", "chance", "to", "tell", "him", "what", "he", "meant", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "All the time.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 383, "question": "And how did you feel when I said good-bye, when I moved on?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "I", "said", "good-bye", ",", "when", "I", "moved", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "I was -- I was --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Same feelings?", "question_tokens": ["Same", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Honestly, I was puzzled because I thought there's no reason for you to retire.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "I", "was", "puzzled", "because", "I", "thought", "there", "'s", "no", "reason", "for", "you", "to", "retire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "\"Cabin Boy\"?", "question_tokens": ["``", "Cabin", "Boy", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "\"Cabin Boy\", yes.", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Cabin", "Boy", "''", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Would you like to buy a monkey?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "buy", "a", "monkey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Big hit -- that's it.", "answer_tokens": ["Big", "hit", "--", "that", "'s", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Not bad, huh?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "bad", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "It was excellent.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "excellent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Any aspirations to become an actor?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "aspirations", "to", "become", "an", "actor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cleveland"]}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "``", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "''", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "And if you're not going to be really good at it, what's the point of wasting everybody's time?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "be", "really", "good", "at", "it", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "point", "of", "wasting", "everybody", "'s", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I did an acting bit in \"Hot in Cleveland\" recently.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "an", "acting", "bit", "in", "``", "Hot", "in", "Cleveland", "''", "recently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pierre"]}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "It's just something to do, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "something", "to", "do", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I played Pierre, a gay hair stylist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "played", "Pierre", ",", "a", "gay", "hair", "stylist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Miller"]}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "George Miller, and when he was a much younger fellow, he had a narrowing -- and he periodically would have to run a hose -- down his esophagus to open it up.", "answer_tokens": ["George", "Miller", ",", "and", "when", "he", "was", "a", "much", "younger", "fellow", ",", "he", "had", "a", "narrowing", "--", "and", "he", "periodically", "would", "have", "to", "run", "a", "hose", "--", "down", "his", "esophagus", "to", "open", "it", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Why are you telling me that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "telling", "me", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I'm just saying.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Now -- but to be more serious about this, you went through a quadruple, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "--", "but", "to", "be", "more", "serious", "about", "this", ",", "you", "went", "through", "a", "quadruple", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "CC", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Quadruple bypass surgery, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Quadruple", "bypass", "surgery", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Jamaica"]}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "He -- he and his family were going to Jamaica.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "--", "he", "and", "his", "family", "were", "going", "to", "Jamaica", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "You remember that night?", "question_tokens": ["You", "remember", "that", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I remember that night and I remember not wanting to go back, not feeling ready to go back, but knowing we had to go back.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "remember", "that", "night", "and", "I", "remember", "not", "wanting", "to", "go", "back", ",", "not", "feeling", "ready", "to", "go", "back", ",", "but", "knowing", "we", "had", "to", "go", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "I mean, wasn't he the light that led everybody through it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "the", "light", "that", "led", "everybody", "through", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "No doubt about it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "doubt", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Well, you have to, because life is no longer solely about you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "to", ",", "because", "life", "is", "no", "longer", "solely", "about", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "But that's the way you feel, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "that", "'s", "the", "way", "you", "feel", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Does he know what you do for a living?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "know", "what", "you", "do", "for", "a", "living", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Does he laugh?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "ETTERMAN: Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["ETTERMAN", ":", "Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Is he a momma's boy or daddy's boy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "momma", "'s", "boy", "or", "daddy", "'s", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Momma's boy for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Momma", "'s", "boy", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "How have you been able to do that year after year?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "been", "able", "to", "do", "that", "year", "after", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "Believe me, I'm embarrassed about it as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Believe", "me", ",", "I", "'m", "embarrassed", "about", "it", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Is it a chore to come up with those?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "chore", "to", "come", "up", "with", "those", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Not for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "How Regina?", "question_tokens": ["How", "Regina", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "She's fine.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Have you had a favorite guest over the years besides me?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "a", "favorite", "guest", "over", "the", "years", "besides", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 842, "question": "Remember that night?", "question_tokens": ["Remember", "that", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 843, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "What are you doing out there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "doing", "out", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "Not now, Dave, I'm in the middle of a show.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "now", ",", "Dave", ",", "I", "'m", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "a", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "Isn't that terrible?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "terrible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "No, it was cute.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "cute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Vespa Scooters"]}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBD", ":", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "Is this why you gave me this car when I left?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "why", "you", "gave", "me", "this", "car", "when", "I", "left", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "You know, that was -- these are so much fun, the Vespa Scooters.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "that", "was", "--", "these", "are", "so", "much", "fun", ",", "the", "Vespa", "Scooters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 880, "question": "You can't ride a bicycle?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "ride", "a", "bicycle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 881, "answer": "It's not the two wheeler.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "the", "two", "wheeler", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 887, "question": "Is Regis here tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Regis", "here", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 888, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 898, "question": "You have heard that before, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "heard", "that", "before", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 899, "answer": "You were nice enough -- You took the Vespa back and you gave me a beautiful watch.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "were", "nice", "enough", "--", "You", "took", "the", "Vespa", "back", "and", "you", "gave", "me", "a", "beautiful", "watch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "Are you wearing it now?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "wearing", "it", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 915, "question": "We're not going to sing?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "sing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 916, "answer": "If you want to sing, you sing.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "want", "to", "sing", ",", "you", "sing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]